<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Manifest CSUVersion="1.0" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="CSUManifest.xsd">
	<UpdateID>13.1.2</UpdateID>
	<OwningChannel><!-- Channel ID which owns this update -->AdobePhotoshopCS6Support-13.0</OwningChannel>
	<TargetBuildType>2</TargetBuildType>
	<DisplayName default="en_US">
		<en_US>Photoshop 13.1.2 for Creative Cloud</en_US>	
		<cs_CZ>Aktualizace aplikace Photoshop 13.1.2 pro službu Creative Cloud</cs_CZ>
		<da_DK>Photoshop 13.1.2 til Creative Cloud-opdatering</da_DK>
		<de_DE>Update für Photoshop 13.1.2 für Creative Cloud</de_DE>
		<es_ES>Actualización de Photoshop 13.1.2 para Creative Cloud</es_ES>
		<fi_FI>Photoshop 13.1.2 -päivitys Creative Cloud -käyttäjille</fi_FI>
		<fr_FR>Mise à jour Photoshop 13.1.2 pour Creative Cloud</fr_FR>
		<fr_MA>Mise à jour Photoshop 13.1.2 pour Creative Cloud</fr_MA>
		<fr_CA>Mise à jour Photoshop 13.1.2 pour Creative Cloud</fr_CA>
		<hu_HU>Photoshop 13.1.2 a Creative Cloud frissítéséhez</hu_HU>
		<it_IT>Aggiornamento Photoshop 13.1.2 per Creative Cloud</it_IT>
		<ja_JP>Creative Cloud アップデート向け Photoshop 13.1.2</ja_JP>
		<ko_KR>Creative Cloud 용 Photoshop 13.1.2 업데이트</ko_KR>
		<nb_NO>Photoshop 13.1.2 for Creative Cloud-oppdatering</nb_NO>
		<nl_NL>Update Photoshop 13.1.2 voor Creative Cloud</nl_NL>
		<pl_PL>Aktualizacja Photoshop 13.1.2 dla usługi Creative Cloud</pl_PL>
		<pt_BR>Atualização do Photoshop 13.1.2 para Creative Cloud</pt_BR>
		<ru_RU>Обновление Photoshop 13.1.2 для Creative Cloud</ru_RU>
		<sv_SE>Uppdatering av Photoshop 13.1.2 för Creative Cloud</sv_SE>
		<tr_TR>Creative Cloud için Photoshop 13.1.2 güncellemesi</tr_TR>
		<uk_UA>Оновлення Photoshop 13.1.2 для Creative Cloud</uk_UA>
		<zh_CN>Creative Cloud 适用的 Photoshop 13.1.2 更新</zh_CN>
		<zh_TW>Creative Cloud 適用的 Photoshop 13.1.2 更新</zh_TW>
		<en_AE>Photoshop 13.1.2 for Creative Cloud</en_AE>	
		<en_IL>Photoshop 13.1.2 for Creative Cloud</en_IL>	
		
	</DisplayName>
	<Description default="en_US">
		<en_US>This Adobe® Photoshop® and Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 update installs new features for Adobe Creative Cloud members and Photoshop subscribers. It offers exciting new capabilities for design, photography and more, including the freedom to nondestructively edit with Blur Gallery and Liquify using new Smart Object support, the ability to export text and shapes as CSS, the option to create Conditional Actions, and support for new HiDPI displays that enable a dramatic improvement in image fidelity and resolution. Other new workflow timesavers are also included. Customers with Photoshop Extended will also receive new 3D options including improved live previews that simplify the creation of shadows and reflections in 3D artwork and a 32-bit color picker for better illumination control, and more.</en_US>
		<cs_CZ>Tato aktualizace aplikací Adobe® Photoshop® a Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 slouží k instalaci nových funkcí pro členy služby Adobe Creative Cloud a předplatitele aplikace Photoshop. Nabízí zajímavé nové možnosti pro návrhy, fotografování atd., mimo jiné nedestruktivní úpravy pomocí galerie rozostření a efektu Zkapalnění s použitím nové podpory inteligentních objektů, schopnost exportovat text a tvary jako šablony stylů CSS, možnost vytváření podmíněných akcí a podporu nových displejů HiDPI, které umožňují výrazné zvýšení věrnosti obrazu a rozlišení. Jsou zde rovněž zahrnuty další nové nástroje pro úsporu času v pracovních postupech. Zákazníci, kteří vlastní aplikaci Photoshop Extended, také získají nové 3D volby včetně živých náhledů, které zjednodušují vytváření stínů a odrazů ve 3D kresbách, výběr 32bitových barev pro lepší ovládání osvětlení a podobně.</cs_CZ>
		<da_DK>Denne opdatering til Adobe® Photoshop® og Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installerer nye funktioner til Adobe Creative Cloud-medlemmer og Photoshop-abonnenter. Den indeholder spændende nye muligheder til design, fotografering og meget mere, herunder friheden til at redigere med Sløringsgalleri og Blødgør uden at ødelægge indholdet, ved hjælp af Smart Object-understøttelse, mulighed for at eksportere tekst og former som CSS, mulighed for at oprette betingede handlinger og support til nye HiDPI-skærme, der dramatisk forbedret billedets naturtrohed og opløsning. Den indeholder også andre funktioner til forkortelse af arbejdsforløbet. Kunder med Photoshop Extended får også nye muligheder til 3D, herunder forbedrede live-eksempler, der gør det nemmere at oprette skygger og refleksioner i 3D-illustrationer samt en 32-bit farvevælger til bedre belysningskontrol og meget mere.</da_DK>
		<de_DE>Bei diesem Update für Adobe® Photoshop® und Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 werden neue Funktionen für Adobe Creative Cloud-Mitglieder und Photoshop-Abonnenten installiert. Es bietet interessante neue Funktionen für Design, Fotografie und mehr, darunter die Möglichkeit, mit der Weichzeichnergalerie und Verflüssigen Bilder mithilfe der neuen Unterstützung für Smart-Objekt nicht-destruktiv zu bearbeiten, Text und Formen als CSS zu exportieren und bedingte Aktionen zu erstellen. Außerdem werden neue HiDPI-Displays unterstützt, die eine enorme Verbesserung in Bezug auf Bildgenauigkeit und Auflösung ermöglichen. Andere Neuigkeiten, die eine Zeitersparnis beim Arbeitsablauf ermöglichen, wurden auch hinzugefügt. Kunden, die Photoshop Extended erworben haben, können sich auch über neue 3D-Optionen freuen, darunter eine verbesserte Live-Vorschau zur einfacheren Erstellung von Schatten und Spiegelungen bei 3D-Bildmaterial, einen 32-bit-Farbwähler für bessere Beleuchtungskontrolle und mehr. </de_DE>
		<es_ES>Esta actualización de Adobe® Photoshop® y Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 instala nuevas funciones para los abonados al programa Adobe Creative Cloud y los suscriptores de Photoshop. Incluye una serie de increíbles funciones nuevas de diseño y fotografía, entre otras, como la libertad de editar de una manera no destructiva con la Galería de efectos de desenfoque y la función Licuar gracias a la nueva compatibilidad con objetos inteligentes; la posibilidad de exportar texto y formas como CSS; la opción de crear acciones condicionales; y la compatibilidad con pantallas HiDPI, lo que supone una enorme mejora en fidelidad y resolución de la imagen. Además, se incluyen más métodos nuevos para ahorrar tiempo en los flujos de trabajo. Los clientes de Photoshop Extended también recibirán nuevas opciones 3D como la previsualización de sombras, que simplifica la creación de sombras y reflejos en imágenes en 3D; y un selector de color de 32 bits que consigue un mayor control de la iluminación, entre otras ventajas. </es_ES>
		<fi_FI>Tämä Adobe® Photoshop®- ja Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 -päivitys sisältää Adobe Creative Cloud -jäsenille ja Photoshop-tilaajille asennettavia uusia toimintoja. Päivitys tarjoaa suunnitteluun, valokuvaukseen ja muuhun työskentelyyn sopivia uusia toimintoja. Esimerkiksi hienovaraiset Sumennusgallerian muokkaukset ja sulatus ovat mahdollisia älykkäiden objektien tuella. Lisäksi tekstiä ja muotoja voi viedä CSS-muodossa, ehdollisten makrojen luominen on mahdollista ja uusia kuvatarkkuutta huomattavasti parantavia HiDPI-näyttöjä tuetaan. Myös muita työnkulkua nopeuttavia toimintoja on mukana. Photoshop Extended -asiakkaat saavat lisäksi uusia 3D-toimintoja, kuten parannetun ajantasaisen esikatselutoiminnon, joka helpottaa varjojen ja heijastusten luomista kolmiulotteisiin teoksiin, ja valaistuksen säätämistä parantavan 32-bittisen värivalitsimen.</fi_FI>
		<fr_FR>Cette mise à jour Adobe® Photoshop® et Adobe Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installe de nouvelles fonctionnalités pour les adhérents à Adobe Creative Cloud et les abonnés Photoshop. Elle élargit les possibilités en matière de dessin, de photographie et autres, en permettant notamment d'effectuer des retouches non destructrices à l'aide de la Galerie d'effets de flou et de la fonction Fluidité grâce à la nouvelle prise en charge d'objet dynamique, d'exporter du texte et des formes en CSS et de créer des actions conditionnelles. Elle prend également en charge les nouveaux écrans HiDPI pour une plus grande fidélité de l'image et une meilleure résolution. De nouveaux mécanismes d'accélération des flux de travail ont également été ajoutés. Les clients utilisant Photoshop Extended auront également accès à de nouvelles options 3D, dont des aperçus directs améliorés qui simplifient le processus de création d'ombres et de reflets dans les illustrations en 3D et un sélecteur de couleurs 32 bits pour un meilleur contrôle de l'éclairage, entre autres améliorations.</fr_FR>
		<fr_MA>Cette mise à jour Adobe® Photoshop® et Adobe Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installe de nouvelles fonctionnalités pour les adhérents à Adobe Creative Cloud et les abonnés Photoshop. Elle élargit les possibilités en matière de dessin, de photographie et autres, en permettant notamment d'effectuer des retouches non destructrices à l'aide de la Galerie d'effets de flou et de la fonction Fluidité grâce à la nouvelle prise en charge d'objet dynamique, d'exporter du texte et des formes en CSS et de créer des actions conditionnelles. Elle prend également en charge les nouveaux écrans HiDPI pour une plus grande fidélité de l'image et une meilleure résolution. De nouveaux mécanismes d'accélération des flux de travail ont également été ajoutés. Les clients utilisant Photoshop Extended auront également accès à de nouvelles options 3D, dont des aperçus directs améliorés qui simplifient le processus de création d'ombres et de reflets dans les illustrations en 3D et un sélecteur de couleurs 32 bits pour un meilleur contrôle de l'éclairage, entre autres améliorations.</fr_MA>
		<fr_CA>Cette mise à jour Adobe® Photoshop® et Adobe Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installe de nouvelles fonctionnalités pour les adhérents à Adobe Creative Cloud et les abonnés Photoshop. Elle élargit les possibilités en matière de dessin, de photographie et autres, en permettant notamment d'effectuer des retouches non destructrices à l'aide de la Galerie d'effets de flou et de la fonction Fluidité grâce à la nouvelle prise en charge d'objet dynamique, d'exporter du texte et des formes en CSS et de créer des actions conditionnelles. Elle prend également en charge les nouveaux écrans HiDPI pour une plus grande fidélité de l'image et une meilleure résolution. De nouveaux mécanismes d'accélération des flux de travail ont également été ajoutés. Les clients utilisant Photoshop Extended auront également accès à de nouvelles options 3D, dont des aperçus directs améliorés qui simplifient le processus de création d'ombres et de reflets dans les illustrations en 3D et un sélecteur de couleurs 32 bits pour un meilleur contrôle de l'éclairage, entre autres améliorations.</fr_CA>
		<hu_HU>Ez az Adobe® Photoshop® és Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 frissítés az Adobe Creative Cloud-tagok és a Photoshop-előfizetők számára telepíti az új funkciókat. Izgalmas új képességeket kínál többek között a tervezők és fényképészek számára: például az új intelligens objektumok támogatják az Életlenítési galéria és Cseppfolyósítás eszközökkel történő visszafordítható képszerkesztést, a szövegek és alakzatok CSS formában exportálhatók, feltételes műveletek hozhatók létre, és támogatja a képhűségben és felbontásban drámai növekedést jelentő új HiDPI kijelzőket. További munkaidő-megtakarítási funkciókkal bővült. A Photoshop Extended szoftert vásárló ügyfelek új 3D funkciókhoz is jutnak, köztük a 3D rajzelemek árnyékainak és tükröződéseinek létrehozását egyszerűsítő javított élő előnézetekkel és a megvilágítás tökéletesebb szabályozását biztosító 32 bites pipettával.</hu_HU>
		<it_IT>Con questo aggiornamento ad Adobe® Photoshop® e Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 vengono installate nuove funzioni per i membri Adobe Creative Cloud e gli utenti iscritti a Photoshop. L'aggiornamento offre nuove funzionalità per design, fotografia e altro ancora, quali: modifica non distruttiva con Galleria sfocatura e Fluidifica e il nuovo supporto per oggetti avanzati; esportazione di testo e forme come CSS; creazione di azioni condizionali; supporto per la nuova visualizzazione HiDPI con notevole miglioramento a livello di fedeltà dell'immagine e risoluzione. Sono inoltre incluse altre funzioni per velocizzare i flussi di lavoro. I clienti con Photoshop Extended riceveranno inoltre le nuove opzioni 3D, quali: anteprime dinamiche per una più facile creazione di ombre e riflessi nella grafica 3D; selettore colore a 32 bit per controllare meglio l'illuminazione; e altro ancora.</it_IT>
		<ja_JP>この Adobe® Photoshop® および Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 アップデートでは、Adobe Creative Cloud メンバーと Photoshop サブスクリプション利用者を対象に新機能をインストールします。デザインや写真などの編集に最適な新機能を備えています。例えば、新しいスマートオブジェクトサポートを利用したぼかしギャラリーやゆがみを使用して、自由な非破壊編集が可能です。テキストやシェイプを CSS として書き出したり、条件付きアクションを作成することもできます。また、画像をより鮮明に表示する新しい HiDPI ディスプレイもサポートしています。他にも、ワークフローを簡素化する便利な機能が含まれています。Photoshop Extended をご利用のお客様には、3D アートワークでシャドウや反射を簡単に作成するライブプレビュー（改良済み）や、より美しいイルミネーション制御を行う 32 bit カラーピッカーなどの新しい 3D オプションも提供されます。</ja_JP>
		<ko_KR>이 Adobe® Photoshop® 및 Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 업데이트는 Adobe Creative Cloud 회원 및 Photoshop 구독자를 위한 새로운 기능을 설치합니다. 이 업데이트는 디자인, 사진 등을 위한 새로운 놀라운 기능을 제공합니다. 이러한 기능에는 새로운 고급 개체 지원을 통해 흐림 효과 갤러리와 픽셀 유동화를 사용하여 비파괴적으로 자유롭게 편집하는 기능, 텍스트와 모양을 CSS로 내보내는 기능, 조건부 액션 만들기 옵션 및 이미지 충실도와 해상도를 대폭 향상시키는 새 HiDPI 디스플레이 지원 기능이 포함되어 있습니다. 작업 과정의 시간을 절약해 주는 기타 새로운 기능도 포함되어 있습니다. Photoshop Extended를 사용하는 고객은 그림자 만들기 및 3D 아트웍의 반사를 용이하게 하는 향상된 실시간 미리 보기, 더 나은 조명 제어를 위한 32비트 색상 피커 등을 포함하는 새로운 3D 옵션을 받게 됩니다. </ko_KR>
		<nb_NO>Denne oppdateringen for Adobe® Photoshop® og Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installerer nye funksjoner for Adobe Creative Cloud-medlemmer og Photoshop-abonnenter. Den gir nye muligheter for design, fotografi og mye annet, inkludert friheten til å redigere med Gjør mindre skarpt-galleri og Gjør flytende med den nye støtten for smarte objekter, muligheten til å eksportere tekst og former som CSS, et alternativ for å opprette betingede handlinger, og støtte for nye HiDPI-skjermer som gir en drastisk forbedring av bildekvalitet og oppløsning. Flere nye, tidsbesparende funksjoner for arbeidsflyt er også inkludert. Kunder med Photoshop Extended får også nye 3D-muligheter, som bedre live-forhåndsvisning som forenkler opprettelsen av skygger og refleksjoner i 3D-prosjekter samt en 32-biters fargevelger for bedre lyskontroll m.m.</nb_NO>
		<nl_NL>Met deze update voor Adobe® Photoshop® en Adobe Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 worden nieuwe functies geïnstalleerd voor Adobe Creative Cloud-leden en Photoshop-abonnees. De update bevat interessante nieuwe mogelijkheden voor ontwerp, fotografie en nog veel meer. Zo zorgt de nieuwe ondersteuning voor slimme objecten ervoor dat u in alle vrijheid bewerkingen met de galerie Vervagen en de functie Uitvloeien kunt uitvoeren zonder dat de oorspronkelijke afbeelding verloren gaat, kunt u tekst en vormen exporteren als CSS en kunt u voorwaardelijke acties maken. Ook worden HiDPI-schermen nu ondersteund, hetgeen zorgt voor een enorme verbetering in de beeldgetrouwheid en resolutie. Ook zijn er nieuwe, tijdbesparende workflows in de update opgenomen. Gebruikers van Photoshop Extended profiteren bovendien van nieuwe 3D-opties, zoals verbeterde live-voorvertoningen waarmee het maken van schaduwen en reflecties in 3D-objecten eenvoudiger wordt, een 32-bits kleurkiezer voor verbeterde belichtinginstelling, en nog veel meer.</nl_NL>
		<pl_PL>Ta aktualizacja programów Adobe® Photoshop® i Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 instaluje nowe funkcje przeznaczone dla członków usługi Adobe Creative Cloud i osób subskrybujących program Photoshop. Oferuje ona wspaniałe nowe rozwiązania ułatwiające projektowanie, obróbkę fotografii i wykonywanie innych zadań. Dzięki obsłudze nowych obiektów inteligentnych umożliwia swobodne, bezpieczne edytowanie przy użyciu narzędzi Galeria rozmyć i Skraplanie. Zapewnia możliwość eksportowania tekstu i kształtów jako kodu CSS oraz opcję tworzenia operacji warunkowych. Obsługuje też nowe wyświetlacze HiDPI — technologii zapewniającej niedoścignioną jakość obrazu i najwyższe rozdzielczości. Aktualizacja obejmuje także inne nowości przyspieszające obiegi pracy. Klienci posiadający program Photoshop Extended otrzymają również dostęp do nowych opcji 3D — takich jak ulepszony aktywny podgląd ułatwiający projektowanie cieni i odbić w kompozycjach 3D oraz 32-bitowy próbnik kolorów gwarantujący precyzyjną kontrolę nad oświetleniem. </pl_PL>
		<pt_BR>Esta atualização para o Adobe® Photoshop® e o Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 instalará novos recursos para os membros do Adobe Creative Cloud e os assinantes do Photoshop. A atualização fornece novas e incríveis capacidades para design, fotografia e muito mais, incluindo liberdade para editar de forma não-destrutiva com a Galeria de desfoque e o filtro Dissolver, utilizando o novo suporte a Objeto inteligente, capacidade de exportar texto e formas como CSS, a opção de criar Ações condicionais, e suporte para novos monitores HiDPI, possibilitando um sensível aumento da fidelidade e da resolução da imagem. Também estão incluídos novos recursos para poupar tempo nos fluxos de trabalho. Os clientes com o Photoshop Extended também receberão novas opções 3D, tais como visualizações ao vivo aprimoradas para simplificar a criação de sombras e reflexos em artes 3D, e um seletor de cores de 32 bits para um maior controle da iluminação, e muito mais.</pt_BR>
		<ru_RU>Данное обновление Adobe® Photoshop® и Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 устанавливает новые функции для пользователей Adobe Creative Cloud и подписчиков Photoshop. Оно обеспечивает новые интересные возможности для дизайна, фотографии и других направлений, в том числе свободу безопасного редактирования с помощью галереи размытия и фильтра «Пластика» благодаря новой поддержке смарт-объектов, возможность экспорта текста и фигур в виде CSS, возможность создания условных действий и поддержу новых дисплеев HiDPI, которая значительно улучшает качество и разрешение изображения. Также включены новые автоматические рабочие процессы. Пользователи Photoshop Extended также получат новые возможности работы в среде 3D, включая улучшенный просмотр в реальном времени, который упрощает создание теней и отражений в 3D-проектов, и 32-битную палитру цветов для улучшения управления освещением, а также многое другое. </ru_RU>
		<sv_SE>Den här uppdateringen för Adobe® Photoshop® och Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 installerar nya funktioner för Adobe Creative Cloud-medlemmar och Photoshop-prenumeranter. Den erbjuder nya spännande funktioner för design, fotografi och annat, exempelvis möjlighet att redigera icke-destruktivt med Oskärpegalleri och Gör flytande via nytt stöd för smarta objekt, möjlighet att exportera text och former som CSS, ett alternativ för att skapa villkorliga villkorliga funktionsmakron och stöd för nya HiDPI-skärmar som ger en drastisk förbättring av bildåtergivningen och upplösningen. Andra nya funktioner som sparar tid i arbetsflödet ingår också. Kunder med Photoshop Extended får också nya 3D-alternativ, bland annat förbättrade liveförhandsgranskningar som gör det enklare att skapa skuggor och reflektioner i 3D-grafik, och en 32-bitars färgväljare som ger bättre belysningskontroll.</sv_SE>
		<tr_TR>Bu Adobe® Photoshop® ve Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 güncellemesi, Adobe Creative Cloud üyeleri ve Photoshop aboneleri için yeni özellikler yükler. Yeni Akıllı Nesne desteğinin kullanımıyla Bulanıklaştırma Galerisi ve Sıvılaştırma özelliği sayesinde zarar vermeden düzenleme özgürlüğü, metni ve şekilleri CSS olarak dışa aktarabilme, Koşullu Eylemler oluşturma seçeneği ve görüntünün aslına uygunluğu ile çözünürlüğünün önemli ölçüde artırılmasını sağlayan yeni HiDPI ekranları desteği dahil olmak üzere tasarım, fotoğrafçılık ve daha fazlasına yönelik heyecan verici yeni özellikler sunar. İş akışına yönelik olarak bunun dışında yeni, zaman kazandıran özellikler de eklenmiştir. Photoshop Extended'a sahip olan müşteriler, 3B resimde gölge ve yansıma oluşturmayı kolaylaştıran geliştirilmiş canlı önizlemelerin dahil olduğu yeni 3B seçenekleri ve daha iyi aydınlatma kontrolü için 32 bit renk seçici vb. özellikleri de elde eder.</tr_TR>
		<uk_UA>Це оновлення Adobe® Photoshop® і Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 інсталює нові можливості для учасників Adobe Creative Cloud і передплатників Photoshop. Воно надає чудові нові функції для оформлення, фотографії тощо, зокрема можливість неруйнівної правки за допомогою галереї розмиття й інструмента «Пластика» з новою функцією підтримки смарт-об’єктів, можливість експортувати текст і фігури як каскадні таблиці стилів (CSS), можливість створення умовних дій і підтримку нових дисплеїв HiDPI, які істотно покращують точність і роздільну здатність зображення. Оновлення також містить інші нові функції, що спрощують і пришвидшують робочий процес. Користувачі Photoshop Extended також отримають нові параметри 3D, зокрема покращений попередній перегляд у реальному часі, який спрощує створення тіней і відображень у 3D-ілюстраціях, 32-бітову палітру кольорів для кращого керування освітленням тощо.</uk_UA>
		<zh_CN>此 Adobe® Photoshop® 和 Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 更新会为 Adobe Creative Cloud 成员及 Photoshop 用户安装新功能，提供令人激动的适用于设计、摄影等的新能力，包括可使用最新的智能对象支持的模糊画廊和液化，自由地进行非破坏性编辑、将文字和形状导出为 CSS 的能力、可建立条件动作的选项，以及支持新 HiDPI 显示以大幅改进图像的真实度和分辨率。另含其他可节省时间的新工作流程。还为 Photoshop Extended 的客户提供新的 3D 选项，包括改进的实时预览，可简化在 3D 作品中建立阴影和反射的流程，以及可提供更好的光照控制的 32 位拾色器，还有其他更多功能。</zh_CN>
		<zh_TW>此 Adobe® Photoshop® 和 Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 更新會為 Adobe Creative Cloud 成員及 Photoshop 訂閱者安裝新功能，提供令人興奮的設計、攝影等新能力，包括可使用最新的智慧型物件支援的模糊收藏館和液化，自由地進行非破壞性編輯、將文字和形狀匯出為 CSS 的能力、可建立條件式動作的選項，以及支援新 HiDPI 顯示以大幅改進影像的真實度和解析度。另包含其他可節省時間的新工作流程。Photoshop Extended 的客戶也會收到新的 3D 選項，包括改良的即時預覽，可簡化在 3D 作品中建立陰影和反射的流程，以及一個可提供更佳照明控制的 32 位元檢色器，還有其他更多功能。</zh_TW>
		<en_AE>This Adobe® Photoshop® and Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 update installs new features for Adobe Creative Cloud members and Photoshop subscribers. It offers exciting new capabilities for design, photography and more, including the freedom to nondestructively edit with Blur Gallery and Liquify using new Smart Object support, the ability to export text and shapes as CSS, the option to create Conditional Actions, and support for new HiDPI displays that enable a dramatic improvement in image fidelity and resolution. Other new workflow timesavers are also included. Customers with Photoshop Extended will also receive new 3D options including improved live previews that simplify the creation of shadows and reflections in 3D artwork and a 32-bit color picker for better illumination control, and more.</en_AE>
		<en_IL>This Adobe® Photoshop® and Photoshop Extended 13.1.2 update installs new features for Adobe Creative Cloud members and Photoshop subscribers. It offers exciting new capabilities for design, photography and more, including the freedom to nondestructively edit with Blur Gallery and Liquify using new Smart Object support, the ability to export text and shapes as CSS, the option to create Conditional Actions, and support for new HiDPI displays that enable a dramatic improvement in image fidelity and resolution. Other new workflow timesavers are also included. Customers with Photoshop Extended will also receive new 3D options including improved live previews that simplify the creation of shadows and reflections in 3D artwork and a 32-bit color picker for better illumination control, and more.</en_IL>
	</Description>
	<AffectedChannels>
		<ChannelID>AdobePhotoshopCS6-13.0</ChannelID>
		<ChannelID>AdobePhotoshopCS664Bit-13.0</ChannelID>
	</AffectedChannels>
	<TargetLicensingType><!-- Retail License Customer -->1</TargetLicensingType>
	<RecommendingChannels>
		<ChannelID>AdobePhotoshopCS6-13.0</ChannelID>
		<ChannelID>AdobePhotoshopCS664Bit-13.0</ChannelID>
	</RecommendingChannels>
	<RequiredChannels>
	</RequiredChannels>
	<Notify>1</Notify>
	<InstallFiles>
		<File RIBSBased="1">
			<Name>Setup.dmg</Name>
			<Type>2</Type>
			<ExecutableName>Adobe Photoshop CS6/AdobePatchInstaller.app</ExecutableName>
			<Size>135017053</Size>
		</File>
	</InstallFiles>
	<NeedsReboot>false</NeedsReboot>
</Manifest>