<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Manifest xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="CSUManifest.xsd" CSUVersion="1.0">
    <UpdateID>12.0.2</UpdateID>
    <OwningChannel>FlashPro12.0</OwningChannel>
    <TargetBuildType>2</TargetBuildType>
    <DisplayName default="en_US">
        <en_US>Flash Pro CS6 update 2</en_US>
		<de_DE>Update 2 zu Flash Pro CS6</de_DE>
		<fr_FR>Mise à jour 2 de Flash Pro CS6</fr_FR>
		<fr_CA>Mise à jour 2 de Flash Pro CS6</fr_CA>
		<it_IT>Aggiornamento 2 di Flash Pro CS6</it_IT>
		<es_ES>Flash Pro CS6, actualización 2</es_ES>
		<es_LA>Flash Pro CS6, actualización 2</es_LA>
		<ja_JP>Flash Pro CS6 アップデート 2</ja_JP>
		<zh_CN>Flash Pro CS6 更新 2</zh_CN>
		<zh_TW>Flash Pro CS6 更新 2</zh_TW>
		<ko_KR>Flash Pro CS6 업데이트 2</ko_KR>
		<nl_NL>Update 2 van Flash Pro CS6</nl_NL>
		<pt_BR>Flash Pro CS6 atualização 2</pt_BR>
		<sv_SE>Flash Pro CS6 uppdatering 2</sv_SE>
		<cs_CZ>Flash Pro CS6 aktualizace 2</cs_CZ>
		<pl_PL>Flash Pro CS6 aktualizacja 2</pl_PL>
		<ru_RU>Обновление 2 Flash Pro CS6</ru_RU>
		<tr_TR>Flash Pro CS6 güncellemesi 2</tr_TR>
    </DisplayName>
    <Description default="en_US">
        <en_US>This update enables Flash Professional CS6 to support the following features exposed by AIR 3.4: 
 
• High-resolution Retina Display Support for AIR Applications on iPad3
• Direct deployment of AIR Applications to iOS devices without using iTunes
• Native iOS simulator support

This update also contains several critical bug fixes. For more information, see Release Notes.
</en_US>
<de_DE>Durch dieses Update wird Flash Professional CS6 die folgenden AIR 3.4-Funktionen unterstützen: 
 
• Unterstützung hochauflösender Retinaanzeige für AIR-Anwendungen auf iPad3
• Direkte Bereitstellung von AIR-Anwendungen für iOS-Geräte ohne die Verwendung von iTunes
• Native iOS-Simulator-Unterstützung

Dieses Update enthält auch mehrere wichtige Bugfixes. Weitere Informationen finden Sie in den Versionshinweisen.
</de_DE>
<fr_FR>Cette mise à jour permet à Flash Professional CS6 de prendre en charge les fonctionnalités suivantes, mises à disposition par AIR 3.4 : 
 
• Prise en charge des écrans Retina haute résolution pour les applications AIR sur iPad3
• Déploiement direct d'applications AIR sur les périphériques iOS sans passer par iTunes
• Prise en charge du simulateur iOS natif

Cette mise à jour corrige également plusieurs bogues critiques. Pour plus d'informations, consultez les notes de mise à jour.
</fr_FR>
<fr_CA>Cette mise à jour permet à Flash Professional CS6 de prendre en charge les fonctionnalités suivantes, mises à disposition par AIR 3.4 : 
 
• Prise en charge des écrans Retina haute résolution pour les applications AIR sur iPad3
• Déploiement direct d'applications AIR sur les périphériques iOS sans passer par iTunes
• Prise en charge du simulateur iOS natif

Cette mise à jour corrige également plusieurs bogues critiques. Pour plus d'informations, consultez les notes de mise à jour.</fr_CA>
<it_IT>Questo aggiornamento aggiunge a Flash Professional CS6 il supporto delle seguenti funzioni esposte da AIR 3.4: 
 
• Supporto del display ad alta risoluzione Retina per le applicazioni AIR su iPad3
• Distribuzione diretta delle applicazioni AIR ai dispositivi iOS senza utilizzare iTunes
• Supporto nativo di iOS Simulator

Questo aggiornamento contiene anche varie correzioni di bug critici. Per ulteriori informazioni, consultate le Note sulla versione.
</it_IT>
<es_ES>Esta actualización permite que Flash Professional CS6 sea compatible con las siguientes funciones expuestas por AIR 3.4: 
 
• Compatibilidad con pantalla Retina de alta resolución para aplicaciones de AIR en iPad3
• Despliegue directo de aplicaciones AIR en dispositivos iOS sin utilizar iTunes
• Compatibilidad nativa con simulador iOS

Esta actualización también incluye soluciones a diversos problemas críticos. Para más información, consulte las Notas de la versión.</es_ES>
<es_LA>Esta actualización permite que Flash Professional CS6 sea compatible con las siguientes funciones expuestas por AIR 3.4: 
 
• Compatibilidad con pantalla Retina de alta resolución para aplicaciones de AIR en iPad3
• Despliegue directo de aplicaciones AIR en dispositivos iOS sin utilizar iTunes
• Compatibilidad nativa con simulador iOS

Esta actualización también incluye soluciones a diversos problemas críticos. Para más información, consulte las Notas de la versión.</es_LA>
<ja_JP>このアップデートによって、Flash Professional CS6 は AIR 3.4 によって実現する以下の機能をサポートできるようになります。 
 
• iPad3 上の AIR アプリケーションに対応する高解像度 Retina ディスプレイのサポート
• iTunes を使用せずに AIR アプリケーションを iOS デバイスに直接デプロイ
• ネイティブ iOS シミュレーターのサポート

このアップデートには、いくつかの重要なバグの修正も含まれます。詳しくは、リリースノートを参照してください。</ja_JP>
<zh_CN>此更新可使 Flash Professional CS6 支持由 AIR 3.4 公开的下列功能： 
 
• 对 iPad3 上 AIR 应用程序的高分辨率 Retina 显示屏支持
• 在不使用 iTunes 的情况下，将 AIR 应用程序直接部署至 iOS 设备
• 本机 iOS 模拟器支持

此更新还包含几种重要的修补程序。有关详细信息，请参见"发行说明"。</zh_CN>
<zh_TW>此更新可讓 Flash Professional CS6 支援由 AIR 3.4 公開的下列功能： 
 
• 對 iPad3 上的 AIR 應用程式的高解析度 Retina 顯示器支援
• 在不使用 iTunes 的情況下，將 AIR 應用程式直接部署到 iOS 裝置
• 原生 iOS 模擬器支援

此更新還包含數種重要的錯誤修正。如需詳細資訊，請參閱「版本說明」。

</zh_TW>
<ko_KR>이 업데이트를 사용하면 Flash Professional CS6에서 AIR 3.4의 다음 기능을 지원할 수 있습니다. 
 
• iPad3의 AIR 응용 프로그램에 대한 고해상도 Retina 디스플레이 지원
• iTunes를 사용하지 않고 iOS 장치에 AIR 응용 프로그램 직접 배포
• 기본 iOS 시뮬레이터 지원

또한 이 업데이트에는 몇 가지 중요한 버그 수정 사항이 포함되어 있습니다. 자세한 내용은 릴리스 정보를 참조하십시오.
</ko_KR>
<nl_NL>Dankzij deze update biedt Flash Professional CS6 ondersteuning voor de volgende functies van AIR 3.4: 
 
• Ondersteuning voor het Retina-display met hoge resolutie voor AIR-toepassingen op iPad3
• Rechtstreekse implementatie van AIR-toepassingen op iOS-apparaten, zonder iTunes te hoeven gebruiken
• Geïntegreerde ondersteuning voor iOS-simulator

Deze update bevat ook enkele belangrijke foutoplossingen. Zie de Release-aantekeningen voor meer informatie.</nl_NL>
<pt_BR>Esta atualização permite que o Flash Professional CS6 oferece suporte aos seguintes recursos expostos pelo AIR 3.4: 
 
• Suporte à tela Retina de alta resolução para aplicativos AIR do iPad3
• Implantação direta de aplicativos AIR em dispositivos iOS sem o uso do iTunes
• Suporte ao simulador de iOS nativo

Esta atualização também contém diversas correções de bug. Para obter mais informações, consulte as Notas da versão.</pt_BR>
<sv_SE>Uppdateringen gör att Flash Professional CS6 stöder följande funktioner i AIR 3.4: 
 
• Stöd för högupplöst Retina-skärm för AIR-program på iPad3
• Direktdistribution av AIR-program till iOS-enheter utan att använda iTunes
• Inbyggt stöd för iOS-simulator

Uppdateringen innehåller även flera kritiska buggfixar. Mer information finns i filen med viktig information.
</sv_SE>
<cs_CZ>Tato aktualizace umožňuje v aplikaci Flash Professional CS6 podporu následujících funkcí používaných v prostředí AIR 3.4: 
 
• Podporu displejů Retina s vysokým rozlišením pro aplikace prostředí AIR na zařízení iPad3
• Přímé nasazení aplikací prostředí AIR do zařízení se systémem iOS bez použití služby iTunes
• Nativní podporu simulátoru systému iOS

Tato aktualizace také obsahuje několik oprav závažných chyb. Další informace najdete v dokumentu Poznámky k vydání.</cs_CZ>
<pl_PL>Ta aktualizacja umożliwia używanie następujących funkcji środowiska AIR 3.4 przez program Flash Professional CS6: 
 
• Obsługa wyświetlaczy o wysokiej rozdzielczości Retina w aplikacjach AIR na tabletach iPad 3
• Bezpośrednie wdrażanie aplikacji AIR na urządzeniach z systemem iOS (bez używania programu iTunes)
• Obsługa natywnego symulatora systemu iOS

Ta aktualizacja usuwa również szereg krytycznych błędów. Więcej informacji można uzyskać w uwagach na temat wersji.
</pl_PL>
<ru_RU>Это обновление позволяет Flash Professional CS6 поддерживать следующие функции, предоставляемые AIR 3.4: 
 
• Поддержка дисплея высокого разрешения Retina для приложений AIR на iPad3
• Непосредственное развертывание приложений AIR на устройства iOS без использования iTunes
• Встроенная поддержка симулятора iOS

В этом обновлении также содержатся несколько критично важных исправлений ошибок. Дополнительные сведения см. в заметках о выпуске.
</ru_RU>
<tr_TR>Bu güncelleme Flash Professional CS6'nın AIR 3.4 tarafından sunulan aşağıdaki özellikleri desteklemesini sağlar: 
 
• iPad3'teki AIR Uygulamaları için yüksek çözünürlüklü Retina Ekran Desteği
• iTunes kullanmadan AIR Uygulamalarını doğrudan iOS cihazlarına dağıtma
• Yerel iOS simulator desteği

Bu güncelleme ayrıca çeşitli önemli hata düzeltmeleri de içermektedir. Daha fazla bilgi için bkz. Sürüm Notları.
</tr_TR>
    </Description>
    <AffectedChannels>
        <ChannelID>FlashPro12.0</ChannelID>
    </AffectedChannels>
    <InstallFiles>
    <File RIBSBased="1">
      <Name>Setup.dmg</Name>
      <Type>2</Type>
      <ExecutableName>Adobe Flash Professional CS6 Update 2/AdobePatchInstaller.app</ExecutableName>
      <Size>588082019</Size>
    </File>
  </InstallFiles>
    <NeedsReboot>false</NeedsReboot>
</Manifest>
